serta.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy | Serta.com

###  Effective Date: October 31st, 2013

We are committed to respecting your privacy at Serta, Inc. (“Serta”). The following Privacy Policy sets forth our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website (our "Website"). **By accessing or using this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection and use of information as discussed in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not access this Website.**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Material changes will be conspicuously posted on the Website. If you have registered with this Website, we will also provide you with email notification of such changes. Your continued use of our Website following notification of such changes constitutes your acceptance of the changes.

Contact Us

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to Serta by emailing [Marketing@serta.com](mailto:marketing@serta.com)

non-us users

 **Serta is a Delaware corporation and the products and services available on this Website are provided by or on behalf of Serta and its licensees based in the united states. The personal information that you provide will be transferred to and maintained in Serta's records in the united states. If you do not consent to this transfer, do not accept this privacy policy or otherwise use the Website.**

information we collect

 _Personally Identifiable Information_

Serta requests your personally identifiable information when you email us at one of the addresses on our "Contact Us" page or otherwise sign up to receive communications from Serta or register with the Website. We also collect your personally identifiable information if you place an order for products via this Website. You may also provide information to Serta and/or its licensees or dealers by filling out information forms at physical store locations. We may collect name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address. If you place an order, we will also collect your shipping address and financial information for payment or financing. **By choosing to provide us with your personally identifiable information you are consenting to the transfer and processing of such information in other countries.**

 _Financial Information_

For security purposes, we do not keep your credit card data in its entirety. We pass all credit card data through to our payment card processor, Authorize.net, and maintain only the last 4 digits in order to help track and confirm any order you place with us.

If you apply online for financing, Serta will also collect any personally identifiable information needed for the credit application, which includes your social security number. In addition to the sharing and disclosure of information set forth below, Serta will share the information submitted with your request for financing with the third party banking institution used by Serta to process such applications. Your information will be used to determine creditworthiness and to administer any approved financing. Serta will keep a copy of such data only until your credit application is approved or declined. This information is not maintained or stored on an on-going basis. In addition, once the financial institution receives your information, your information is subject to the bank's privacy policy and the bank may use your personal information to contact you to offer additional bank services, such as credit card services. If you wish to be removed from the bank's mailing list you must contact the bank directly.

When you browse our Website, you are able to do so anonymously. Serta also collects certain information via this Website that is not personally identifiable.

 _Analytics_

Like many websites, we use a third party service provider, such as Google Analytics, to collect information about your use of our Website. We track data about traffic to our Website and your visit to and experience on our Website, which information we use to improve our Website structure and content.

 _Cookies_

Serta may use cookies to track the use of our Website and to facilitate and enhance your experience on our Website. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies enable us to facilitate access to different aspects of our Website. For example, by showing when and how you and others visit our Website, cookies help us to see which pages of the Website are popular and which are not. Cookies can also help us to improve your enjoyment of this Website, for example, by remembering your address or other personal information when you request information or services on the Website.

We use session cookies during the time of your visit on the Website that expire when you exit and we also use more permanent cookies that are two year tracking cookies so we can recognize you if you return to the Website. If you add any item to your shopping cart during a session, we also use a 30-day cookie to track your shopping cart.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable this function so that your browser will not accept cookies. Please be aware that disabling this function may impact your use and enjoyment of this Website.

 _Third Party Cookies And Ad Choices_

We use third party ad networks (called third-party ad servers or network advertisers) to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These third party ad networks may place their cookies, web beacons or other technology on this Website or in your browser to collect non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit this Website to enable those third party ad networks to deliver advertisements for our products to you on third party websites. We encourage you to view the privacy policy of advertisers and ad services to learn more about their cookies and other technologies.

If you do not want to receive those kinds of advertisements, look for the "Ad Choices" icon in the advertisements, which will contain a link to the privacy policy of the ad network that will provide you with information on how to opt-out of receiving such targeted advertising.

 **You can also visit the website[http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to change your consumer preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain further information about third party ad networks and online behavioral advertising.**

 _Aggregated Information_

In addition, we may take personally identifiable information you provide to us and aggregate it with information of other users and customers such that the data no longer identifies you. We may use and share aggregated information that does not uniquely identify you when it enables us to improve and enrich our services and Website content.

 _IP Addresses_

Serta logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes and to track geographic analytics to help us determine where our Website users are located. IP addresses are not used to track a user’s session. This information only helps us determine how often different areas of our site are visited. We do not link IP address to any information that is personally identifiable.

For example, as part of the Website services, we can assist you in finding a dealer. We do so by collecting your IP address and/or your zip code to provide you with the information of the dealer nearest you.

Like most other Websites, Serta’s servers automatically track certain information about your activity on our Website. This information allows us to keep our Website running efficiently. This information includes: the browser you are using (such at Netscape, Internet Explorer, etc.); your operating system (such as Macintosh, Windows XP, etc.); your IP address; and the referring URL and all Serta URLs you visit.

 _Other Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

We may also use web beacons and pixel tags. Web beacons (also called single pixel gifs or web bugs) are Internet tools, such as transparent images on the website or in e-mails that we may send you, that help us to determine, for instance, whether a page has been viewed or an e-mail opened. For example, when you ask us to send you information, we may use web beacons to determine how many of the e-mails we sent were actually opened. A pixel tag is a type of web beacon embedded in an image on the website. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including a banner ad, may contain a pixel tag.

 _Data Linking_

If you register with this Website, nonpersonally identifiable information about your use and movement on the Website will be linked to your registration and may be stored and maintained in connection with your account.

 _Digital Fingerprinting_

In the event you submit an application for financing, our service providers may use certain technological measures and third party databases and services to engage in digital fingerprinting. This technology passively collects information about your device to develop a digital identifier for your device, which is then stored on your device to identify the device in various online transactions. This information is combined with other information regarding your use of the Website and third party databases in order to identify fraud risks and reduce online fraud. The device data that is collected by our service providers may be maintained to create a history and reputation of a particular device to help reduce online fraud.

data use, sharing and your choices

We may use the personally identifiable information that you provide so that we may send you the information and materials you request or otherwise contact you as you request.

You may also opt-in to receiving additional marketing communications from Serta and its authorized licensees, dealers and distributors for marketing and other purposes communicated to you. If you choose to opt-in to such communications, we will use your personally identifiable information for the purpose indicated and we will share your information with one or more Serta authorized licensees, dealers or distributors. If you choose to opt-out of any such communications, you may do so at any time and without penalty by clicking on the link provided in the email to unsubscribe or by contacting us at the number provided. We will also use your information to process any order you may place or otherwise provide you about information regarding your product, such as any recall notices. You may not unsubscribe to communications regarding your order or product. Unsubscribing to marketing communications from Serta will remove you from our marketing database, but we will still need to communicate with you about your order or other request.

In addition to sharing your information with authorized dealers, we may share your information with our affiliates, licensees, vendors, service providers and agents who assist us in providing our products and services and processing your orders and payments, such as our call center and vendors that provide warehousing and delivery, marketing and advertising, data aggregation, hosting, data verification, statistical analysis and order processing. We require our vendors, service providers and agents to keep your information confidential and they are not permitted to use your information for any purpose other than providing services to Serta.

Finally, we will share your information if required by law to do so, when required to legally protect and defend the rights or property of Serta, when Serta believes it appropriate to protect its users, employees, or the public, and when required to enforce or defend the conditions of any agreement with Serta, including without limitation the Terms of Use or Terms & Conditions of Purchase.

In the event that Serta or its business assets (or those of any authorized dealer) are bought, sold, or otherwise transferred or reorganized, the transferred business assets will likely include the information that has been collected and will be transferred to the new owner, who will continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

finance offers

At certain points during your visit to our Website, we may check whether you are pre-qualified for available finance offers. We will use your name, address and other account information we have collected to check whether you might be pre-qualified for any available finance offers. We will provide an onscreen notice of our pre-qualification check. These checks do not impact your credit score and are only preliminary checks for available offers. Your request for any available offer may be declined if your full application shows you do not qualify for such offer.

If you choose to request any finance offers that may be available to you, we will then request additional information from you for your qualification application, which will be submitted to our finance partner as part of the review, processing, and either acceptance or rejection of your application.

links from this website

This policy only addresses Serta’s collection and use of your information from this Website, except as otherwise provided. If you disclose your information to others in connection with your use of our Website, or any other Website (including sites linked to our Website), you are subject to the privacy policies that they apply. Serta does not have control over the privacy policies applied by any other party that you may disclose information to when linking to or from our Website. If you would like information on any other party's privacy policy, you should contact that party directly, and we encourage you to do so.

security

Serta employs standard industry measures to help protect the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, including the use of firewalls, intrusion prevention systems, and SSL encryption. We use Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt information, including credit card numbers or other customer information, before it travels the Internet.

Please understand, despite these efforts, we cannot guarantee the security of your information given the current state of the Internet. We cannot guarantee protection of all electronic information from interception, misappropriation, misuse or alteration. We cannot guarantee that your information will not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or the unauthorized acts of third parties.

access by children

Our Website is not intended for children and we will not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose online. If you discover your child has provided us with personally identifiable information, you may contact us , as described in the first paragraph of this policy if you would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our databases upon receiving your request.

updating your information

If you wish to update, correct or otherwise have access to your personally identifiable information in our records, please contact us with your request as set forth above in Contact Us.
